Kept Woman is a thriller, tv movie, mystery film directed by Michel Poulette.
Jessica and her fiancé Evan just moved from the city into
their dream home on a quiet suburban street.
Soon after, Jessica catches her seemingly friendly new neighbor,
Simon, in a strange lie and can't let her suspicions rest.
The danger escalates when Simon lures her inside his home and imprisons Jessica in his
secret bunker, meticulously decorated in the idealized style of the 1950's.
Jessica, played by Courtney Ford.
Simon, played by Shaun Benson.
Evan, played by Andrew W. Walker.
Robin, played by Rachel Wilson.
Tyler, played by Troy Blundell.
Oscar, played by Jesse Camacho.
Courtney Ford (born June 27, 1978) is an American actress.
She is best known for her roles on television, such as playing Christine Hill on Dexter (2009), Portia Bellefleur on True Blood (2011), Lily on Parenthood (2012), Tonia
Pyne on Murder in the First (2014), Kate Taylor on Revenge (2014), Kelly Kline on Supernatural (2016–2018) and Nora Darhk on Legends of Tomorrow (2017–2021).
She also played the lead role in the Lifetime television film Kept Woman (2015).
The tone is mind_bending and intense.